{
    "id": "59a349a0d1824fd49f49d67f6a27278b",
    "title": "Possessive Pronouns Or Possessive Adjectives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "That is ......................... place. Which is .........................?",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "my, your",
                "mine, your",
                "my, yours"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "35edeed0c2d84d1f8fcbbd6a0fa87bfb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did ..................................... parents arrive on time?",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec0ccf6684af4a4ab17c533e4105519f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She had the time of .................................. life.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "401e12be6f814d1684a2a4fb2d901a17"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is ................................ Which is ..............................?",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "mine, your",
                "mine, yours",
                "my, yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cfbebbf0b15a4f1d88858a805f97d1f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever been to ..................................... house?",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec8a197c5cfa488f83d6cd42e9a567bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a friend of ..................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "024cac3bb093442ba7cee1c0e6cd4d70"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog has had ..................................... breakfast.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "its",
                "it's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81410ba4b178455dbc78d528937a2513"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is none of ................................... business.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7a6362a4c604e5a801cb6856be06da4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mind ................................ own business.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "127741a9ec114ff8b2921a4ee8f5a37f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are these books ...............................?",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4cdb33f33724823b54924501ba3e989"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is .................................... land. That is ..............................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "our, their",
                "our, theirs",
                "ours, theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8885f756130b4ca78e91ca55a9c73061"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a friend of ........................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, your, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns. The words mine, his, hers, yours, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone.",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "200b5f2427884147b93461f5455a5b52"
        }
    ]
}